

DHEERAJ KUMAR

Personal Information

Address

Lokpriya Vihar khora colony Ghaziabad

Phone

9667789061, 7562058728

Email

dheerajaskumar.92@gmail.com

Additional Skills

- Customer service
- Time management
- Customer retention
- Problem solving approach
- Empathy mapping
- Team performance

Hobbies

Cooking

Professional Summary

"Customer service professional with more than 2 years of experience working in BPO Industries. Consistent positive interactions with customers and knowledge of time management have resulted in a promotion to team leader. Proven ability to provide excellent customer service in busy environments. Ability to adapt to customers' needs and match them with the right solutions."

Work Experience

09/2020-07/2022

Wipro Limited, Greater Noida

- Sr Customer service representative
- Amazon UK International Voice(domain)
- I was hired a role of SR. Customer service Associate for AMAZON UK Voice/Non-voice(Domain), I've handled a very large amount of Inbound calls/chats on daily basis, The basic role of mine is that Attending a calls and chats, Understand the customer issues, resolve the concerns and queries of each and every customer. Also I've maintain a records of all the interaction takes place. & I have raised a appropriated follow-up's with the customer. Incase I have unable to provide satisfactory resolution to the customer then my

duty is to escalate such query to Appropriate concern department.

10/2019-06/2020

Tech Mahindra Limited, Noida

- Customer service representative
- Vodaphone postpaid Voice(domain)
- I was hired a role of customer service associate for VODAFONE POSTPAID Voice(Domain). I have handled a very large amount of Inbound calls on daily basis, The basic role of mine is that Attending a calls, understand the customer issues, resolve the concerns and queries of each and every customer. I have maintain a records of all the interaction takes place. And I have raised a appropriated follow-up's with the customer.

Education

04/2013-08/2017

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University Hyderabad.

- Bachelors In Technology
- Mechanical engineering

Languages

English — Proficient

Hindi — Proficient